Dániel Dénes



denes.daniel93@gmail.com



linkedin.com/in/leinadsened



https://leinadsened.github.io

Summary

4 years working experience in chemical engineering, started a career change in the beginning of 2022's summer with Green Fox's junior software tester bootcamp. During the bootcamp I really enjoyed the first week's coding tasks, so I started The Odin's Project simultaniously, to spice up my learning with web development.

So far I've finished the manual testing part of the bootcamp, and I'm curious if I can get hired to continue my learning in "real world" situations!

Experience



Chemist

Organofil Kft.

Sep 2018 - Aug 2019 (1 year)

Organic chemical production in kilo-lab, maintence of the lab and optimization of the production process.

Technologist Assistant

Egis Pharmaceuticals PLC

Feb 2017 - Aug 2018 (1 year 7 months)

Preparation of validation plans and reports, data analysis and database management.

Education

Budapest University of Technology and Economics

Bachelor's degree, Chemical Engineering 2012 - 2018

Green Fox Academy

Junior Software Tester Jul 2022 - Dec 2022

Budapest University of Technology and Economics

112/120 credits completed, Process Engineering 2019 - 2022

Skills

HTML • Cascading Style Sheets (CSS) • Python (Programming Language) • Microsoft Office • Microsoft Excel • JavaScript • Hugo